

Brian Moreira, 29 years old 2D Artist hey@brianmoreira.com +55 (21) 9 2020-8221 Teresópolis, RJ - Brazil https://brianmoreira.com/en/

Hi there! I'm Brian. Over the last few years, I've been working as an User Interface and User Experience Designer (also known as UI/UX). But right now, I'm studying illustration, 2D animation, character rigging, painting (digital and traditional) to become a 2D Artist capable of working in animations (by animating characters or painting backgrounds) as much as illustrating children's books, etc.

Soft Skills: Creativity, Collaborative Work, Adaptability, Resilience, Empathy and Professional Integrity.

Hard Skills: 2D Animation, Digital Painting, Traditional Painting, Pixel Art.

Softwares: Toon Boom Harmony, Krita, Figma, Adobe Photoshop, After Effects e Premiere.

Experience

Job: UI/UX Designer (Intermediate)

Company: Fintera

City: Teresópolis, , Rio de Janeiro, Brazil (Remote)

Period: 2020 - 2023

Three years at Fintera, since its creation, working with UI/UX Design, elaborating and drawing screens and improvements for an application, through the software Figma.

Job: Designer & Front-end Developer (Intermediate)

Company: Nexaas

City: Rio de Janeiro - São Paulo, Brazil

Period: 2015 - 2019

During almost four years working at Nexaas as a Designer and Front-end Dev, for the most part at the Marketing team responsible for the implementation of layouts and alterations of every product's websites and commercial pages from the company. Relocated by the company from the office at Rio to the office in São Paulo in 2019.

Job: Web Designer

Company: DeBra Tecnologia

City: Teresópolis, Rio de Janeiro, Brazil

Period: 2012 - 2014

Job: Web Design Internship

Company: Shopp Mídia Comunicação **City:** Teresópolis, Rio de Janeiro, Brazil

Period: 2010 - 2012

Formation

Graduation

Graphic Design Technologist - Complete Graduation

Universidade Estácio de Sá Rio de Janeiro 2014 - 2017

Courses

Computer Graphics - Graphic Design, Web

Development and Post-Production Seven Computação Gráfica Rio de Janeiro 2013 - 2014

English (Complete)

lebeu / Progresso Teresópolis 2008 - 2013

Cinematic Form and Style

Cinema em Cena / Pablo Villaça Rio de Janeiro 2017 (Carga horária de 15 horas)

Theory, Language and Film Criticism

Cinema em Cena / Pablo Villaça Rio de Janeiro 2014 (Carga horária de 15 horas) **Drawing I**

Quanta Academia de Artes São Paulo - EAD 2020 - Atualmente cursando

Basic Drawing

Impacto Quadrinhos Rio de Janeiro 2012 - 2013

Advanced Animation

Anima Mundi / Cesar Coelho Rio de Janeiro 2018 (Carga horária de 36 horas)

Basic Animation Workshop

Anima Mundi / Aída Queiroz Rio de Janeiro 2018 (Carga horária de 30 horas)